Richard! Hello.
Richard! 你好.
I hope I haven't kept you waiting very long.
我没有让你们等很长时间吧.
No, no. We just arrived.
没有, 没有.我们也刚刚到.
Nancy, this is Constanza Fuentes.
Nancy, 这位是Constanza Fuentes.
Constanza, my wife Nancy.
Constanza, 这是我妻子Nancy.
I am so pleased to meet you.
认识你很高兴.
Listen, let's go upstairs.
我说, 咱们上楼吧.
I'd love to show you around.
我带你们到处看看.
Is it Nancy Hobart,
你是叫Nancy Hobart,
or did you keep your own name?
还是姓你娘家的姓?
It's Hobart.
我姓Hobart.
I took Richard's name when we got married.
我和Richard结婚时就改随他的姓了.
Oh, I took my husband's name, too.
Oh, 我也是姓我丈夫的姓.
But that was a long time ago.
不过那是很久以前的传统了.
These days, many women don't.
如今, 很多女性都不改随夫姓了.
At the time, it was more trouble to keep my own name than to change it to his.
我们结婚那会儿, 要是不改随夫姓的话会很麻烦的.
So we gave mine to our daughter as a middle name.
不过我女儿的中间名用的是我的姓.
Your daughter is Beth, right?
你女儿叫Beth, 对吧?
Elizabeth Jane Ellis Hobart.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, 这名宇真好听.
It sounds like an author's name, doesn't it?
听上去像是作家的名字, 对吗?
I think it sounds like an attorney's name.
我倒觉得听上去像是律师的名字.
And what does Beth think?
Beth觉得呢?
She'd like to think it's the name of a great tennis player.
她希望她的名字听起来像是位了不起的网球运动员.
I'm glad to hear it.
那我太高兴了.
You know the families of candidates are often in the public eye.
要知道候选人的家庭成员经常会受到公众的注意.
Some kids have a hard time with it.
有些孩子会觉得受不了.
But perhaps that daughter of yours wouldn't mind it so much.
不过也许你们的女儿不大会介意这些.
We'll see.
那也得以后才知道.
It's all very new to her the idea of her father as a celebrity.
毕竟父亲要做名人这件事她还是头一次碰到.
Nancy...
A minor celebrity.
我是说有点儿小名气的人.
Oh, no, Nancy.
Oh, 不, Nancy.
If we are going to have a celebrity,
我们要是想让他做名人的话,
let's do it in a big way.
那就让他做个大名人.
Let's have a star!
让我们也有一个明星!